DONOVAN WILLIAMS

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

678) 294-1056

DONOVAN122@YAHOO.COM

HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/I

N/DONOVAN-WILLIAMS615036B9/

PROFILE

I am a full stack web developer with several years of experience in the IT field. I am a good problem solver, able to grasp new concepts quickly and have a desire for life long learning. My technical skills include express, react, ruby on rails, SQL, C#. Seeking a position to maximize my, quality assurance, program development, and training experience.

SKILLS

- React
- Express
- Ruby On Rail
- SQL
- JavaScript
- Html/css
- node
- Analytical thinking, planning
- Project management
- Strong communication skills
- Accuracy and attention to details

USEFUL LINKS

GIT HUB: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/THEDON122

LINKEDIN: HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/DONOVAN-WILLIAMS-615036B9/

A LIVE PROJECT HTTPS://YOUNG-FJORD-21221.HEROKUAPP.COM/

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

GENERAL ASSEMBLY | MAR 2018 - PRESENT

- Used React, Express, Ruby on Rails to create application and websites that were responsive and to use data from internal databases and third party apis
- Further developed my skills in analytical thinking and problem-solving, as well-as reinforce the importance of attention to detail

JUNIOR DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR

LB HODGES INC | AUG 2016- - JAN 2018

- Troubleshoot ERPNext for issues involving Human Resource systems and accounting systems.
- Backup and restore databases as necessary.

SHAREPOINT DEVELOPER

KNACKTEK | JUL 2014 - AUG 2016

- Successfully planed and impalement web interface design.
- Insured data integrate of legacy systems.

EDUCATION

CERTIFICATION WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE
GENERAL ASSEMBLY | 2018 - 2018

ASSOCIATES OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE
GWINNETT TECHNICAL COLLEGE | 2012 - 2015

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BUSINESS MANAGEMENT
ARGOSY UNIVERSITY | 2008 - 2011

CERTIFICATIONS

COMPTIA

A+ CERTIFICATION

COMPTIA

NETWORK+ CERTIFICATION

GWINNETT TECHNICAL COLLEGE

NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR CERTIFICATE